American Star is a thriller, mystery, drama film
directed by Gonzalo López-Gallego.
An assassin on a final assignment in
Fuerteventura, to kill a man he has never met.
When his target is delayed, he finds himself drawn to the
island, people and a ghostly shipwreck.
Instead of following protocol he stays.
But when the target returns, the world has shifted.
Before everything was simple, now nothing is.
Wilson, played by Ian McShane.
Gloria, played by Nora Arnezeder.
Ryan, played by Adam Nagaitis.
Thomas, played by Thomas Kretschmann.
Anne, played by Fanny Ardant.
Cowboy, played by Andrés Gertrúdix.
American Star is a 2024 British thriller film directed by Gonzalo López-Gallego,
written by Nacho Faerna, and produced by Ian McShane and Michael Elliott.
The film stars McShane, Thomas Kretschmann, Nora Arnezeder,
Adam Nagaitis, Fanny Ardant, and Oscar Coleman.
American Star was released in theaters and also digitally on 26 January 2024 in the United States
by IFC Films, and in the United Kingdom on 23 February 2024 by Vertigo Releasing.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and intense.